[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All but three European Union official languages are from the Indo-European family. They are Finnish, Estonian and which other language?", "correct_answer": "Hungarian", "incorrect_answers": ["Greek", "Polsih", "Bulgarian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors is not in the movie Over Her Dead Body?", "correct_answer": "Sarah Hills", "incorrect_answers": ["Kali Rocha", "Eva Longoria", "Jason Biggs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star wars character delivered the words, I cant. Its too big.?", "correct_answer": "Luke Skywalker", "incorrect_answers": ["Han Solo", "Leia", "Yoda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city in the state of Oregon is known as The City of Roses?", "correct_answer": "Portland", "incorrect_answers": ["Astoria", "Corvallis", "Salem"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Daddy Warbucks is a character in this popular musical that opened in April 21, 1977.", "correct_answer": "Annie", "incorrect_answers": ["Xanadu", "Phantom of the Opera", "Cats"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress, named Sarah, is not correctly matched with the TV show in which she appeared?", "correct_answer": "Sarah Paulson - All My Children (Kendall Hart)", "incorrect_answers": ["Sarah Chalke - Scrubs (Dr. Elliot Reid)", "Sarah Michelle Gellar - Buffy the Vampire Slayer (Buffy)", "Sarah Joy Brown - General Hospital (Carly Corinthos)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following cheeses is a hard cheese?", "correct_answer": "Emmental", "incorrect_answers": ["Lyonnais", "La Vache Qui Rit", "Formaggio di capra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many vertebrae make up the thoracic region of the spinal column?", "correct_answer": "12", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "7", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a Magic: The Gathering game format?", "correct_answer": "One Eyed Cyclops", "incorrect_answers": ["Two Headed Giant", "Free For All", "Emporer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song does the movie High School Musical 3 start out with?", "correct_answer": "Now or Never", "incorrect_answers": ["Start of Something New", "Can I Have This Dance", "Scream"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1987 film received the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 60th Academy Awards in 1988?", "correct_answer": "The Last Emperor", "incorrect_answers": ["Hope and Glory", "Fatal Attraction", "Moonstruck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It was a war fought because a  Prussian prince was put on the Spanish throne.", "correct_answer": "The Franco-Prussian War", "incorrect_answers": ["The  War of  Prussian Succession", "The War of  Spanish Succession", "The Iberian Campaign"]}]